

# CÉDRIC KNAPP

Content Creation Project Management

#### CONTACT



**Telephone** +41 77 425 60 66



eMail

cedric.knapp@outlook.com



**Address** 

Breitestrasse 52 8400 Winterthur

## **ABOUT ME**

Do you remember your first kiss? The anticipation leading to it? The excitement pulsating in your chest, building up to a final moment of truth? Great. Because that's what your users should experience clicking a conversion button.



**Birthday** 23.09.1990

# **LANGUAGES**

German	••••
English	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
French	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Italian	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
Spanish	•0000



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Eyekon AG since 2018

#### **Projekt Manager**

Managing customer projects in a 360° digital agency, from offer to support. Budgeting, task management, controlling, communication, coordination design & engineering (IT)...

**Senior Content Creator & Strategist** 

Concept & production of multimedia content (external & internal). Brand stories, claims, UX writing, PR copy, storyboards, videos,ccampaigns, whitepapers, social media, content modelling & strategies...

20 Minuten 2015-2017

#### **Editor**

Concept & production of editorial articles, research, interviews, srtory development. photography, creative planning...

#### Video Lead

Lead video production departement Zurich, Concept, filming, production video & audio, post production...

Various
Positions
2010-2015

Internships and Student Jobs
Internship journalism (20 Minuten),

media / data analysis (Argus der Presse AG)...

Sideline:

Tauchstation since 2020

**Creative Director and Host** 

Political news on Instagram (@tauch.station)



## **EDUCATION**

University of Zurich 2011-2015

**Bachelor of Arts** 

Major: Media & Communication Minor: Management & Economics

Sydney, Australia 2011 Language Stay

Sydney English Language Center



## **SKILL CLOUD**

